# Gabriele G. Falloon

Full Stack Web Developer with a background of high-quality reporting, leading and sales - a lifelong learner. Known for successful teamwork along with clean and effective coding. Innovative, goal-driven, organized and energetic professional.

San Antonio, TX 78255 ggfalloon@gmail.com Phone | 214-929-1872

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/gabriele-falloon | Github: github.com/ggfalloon | Portfolio: ggfalloon.github.io/Portfolio/

#### **PROJECTS**

#### Pill Box - 2021

sheltered-caverns-06883.herokuapp.com/ | github.com/ggfalloon/Pill-Box Joined with a team of 3 to create a full stack, Heroku deployed, mobile-first application that allows the user or caretaker to save patients and the medications they need to stay organized and reduce errors.

 Tools used: HTML5/CSS3, Bootstrap CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Node.js, Handlebars, MySQL, Sequelize

#### Better Weather - 2020

ggfalloon.github.io/BETTER-WEATHER/ | github/ggfalloon/BETTER-WEATHER Worked with a team of 3 to produce a mobile-first web app that provides odds data, outdoor conditions and stadium information appealing to the user who wishes to place an informed wager on NFL football games.

• Tools used: HTML5, TailwindCSS, JavaScript, jQuery, AJAX: API

#### **Employee Tracker - 2020**

github.com/ggfalloon/EmployeeTracker

A Nodejs command line application for easily managing company employees, utilizing MySQL.

Tools used: HTML5/CSS3, JavaScript, JQuery, MySQL, Node.js, inquirer

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# Elevate Bartending, Austin, TX — Director of Events 2018 - 2020

- Contributed to 600% growth in sales in the first year of employment.
- Remotely managed all incoming leads and converted 30-40% to bookings.
- Assisted in development and maintenance of the company's new website.
- Using Google Sheets, created and maintained essential spreadsheets for tracking sales records, payroll, events, etc.
- Detailed events for both Austin and San Antonio locations and led execution of San Antonio events.

#### Legacy Church, Plano, TX — Office Manger/Church Clerk 2012 - 2015

- Maintained and updated software database. Improved and developed various Excel reports.
- Managed/recruited volunteers, on-boarded new staff, supply budget, organized events, calendars & phone systems.
- Co-led initiative to reduce energy costs through wifi enabled programmable thermostats.

# Hudson & Marshall of Texas, Plano, TX — Account Lead 2007 - 2011

- Promoted to Contract Administrator within 3 months of initial hire date.
- Received a second promotion to Account Lead as liaison for the company's servicing clients. Assisted in developing essential client reporting using Excel's macro and pivot table functions.
- Attended multiple real estate auctions throughout the country, completing various tasks to ensure smooth transactions for buyers, investors and real estate agents.

## **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

#### Languages/Frameworks:

HTML5/CSS3, JavaScript/JQuery, Bootstrap, JSON, AJAX/API, React, Node.js, Express.js, MySQL, OOP

**Other:** Git/Github, Terminal, Microsoft Office, Google Suite, Zoom, Hangouts

#### **EDUCATION**

University of Texas at San Antonio, San Antonio, TX

Certified Full Stack Web Developer

**Richland College, Dallas, TX**Microcomputer Applications

Stephen F. Austin State
University, Nacogdoches, TX
General Business

## **AFFILIATIONS**

# **Association for Computing Machinery**

Student Member